Guide to the William R. George family papers, 1750-1989.
George, William R. family papers, 1750-1989.
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Albertson, Henry H.; Kirkland, Eleanor G., May 1936 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Dicker, Martin; Sargent, Noel; Stoddart, Bessie D., May 1936 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Dicker, Martin, May 1936 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Broadhurst, Iva; Freeborn, Edith G.; Dawson, Charles B.; LeRoy, Harris G.; Bartol, Leah; Gauffin, Einar, May 1936 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Bartol, Leah; Smith, Jacob G.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Kirkland, Eleanor G. (Annotations.), Jun. 1936 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Forbes, Alexander; Kirkland, Eleanor G., Jun. 1936 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - LeRoy, Betty; Kinane, John J.; McClelland, Pauline Brooks; Freeborn, Edith G.; Miller, Gerrit Smith; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Rockwell, Vera C.; Forbes, Alexander; Smith, Jacob G., Jul. 1936 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    Esther B. George's letters to participants in memorial service to William R. George; Vera C. Rockwell correspondence pertaining to the preparation of The Adult Minor by William R. George; National Association of Junior Republics.
  - Memorial Address by Jacob G. Smith; Daddy George Memorial Committee; Address by Alexander Forbes; :Daddy George as Patriot" by Lyman Beecher Stowe. (Annotations.), Jul. 1936 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Memorial Addresses by Lyman Beecher Stowe and Jacob G. Smith, Jul. 1936 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Morse, Charles E.; King, Ruth; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; King, Edward M.; Smith, Jacob G.; Forbes, Alexander; Rockwell, Vera C. (Annotations.), Aug. 1936 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Rockwell, Vera C.; Smith, Jacob G.; Dicker, Martin; Morse, Charles E. (Annotations.), Sept. - Oct.1936 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Dicker, Martin; Smith, Jacob G.; Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Hotchkiss, Irma H. (Annotations.), Nov. 1936 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Dwight, Richard E.; Rockwell, Vera C.; Smith, Jacob G.; Stoddart, Bessie D., Dec. 1936 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Rockwell, Vera C., 1936 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    Daddy George Memorial Fund; "Socialism in Religion."
  - Kinane, John J.; Smith, Jacob G.; Dicker, Martin; Rockwell, Vera C.; Hotchkiss, Willard E., May - Sep.1936 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Kinane, John J.; Hotchkiss, Willard E., Oct. - Dec.1936 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    William R. George funeral callers, arrangements.
  - McAllister, Peter F.; Smith, Jacob G.; Rockwell, Vera C.; Broadhurst, Iva, Jan. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Rockwell, Vera C.; Smith, Jacob G., Feb. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Jacob G.; Rockwell, Vera C., Mar. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Feldman, Mary E.; Kinane, John J.; McLelland, William F., Apr. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Jacob G.; Hammon, F.H., May 1937 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Dawson, Charles B. (Annotations.), May 1937 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Smith, Jacob G.; Kinane, John J.; Rockwell, Jacob C., Jun. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Rockwell, Vera C., Jun. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Smith, Jacob G.; Rockwell, Vera C.; Wickware, F.G., Jul. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    F.G. Wickware correspondence pertaining to the publication of The Adult Minor by William R. George. (Annotations.)
  - Wickware, F.G.; Rockwell, Vera C., Aug. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Freeborn, Malcolm J.; Rockwell, Vera C.; Smith, Jacob G.; Wickware, F.G., Sept. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Smith, Jacob G.; Rockwell, Vera C.; Freeborn, Malcolm J., Sept. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Rockwell, Vera C.; Schaeffer, C. Gibson; Wickware, F.G.; Smith, Jacob G., Sept. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Rockwell, Vera C.; Wickware, F.G.; Freeborn, Malcolm J.; Smith, Jacob G.; Levin, Leonard S., Oct. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    William R. George death certificate.
  - Kirkland, Eleanor G.; McCormick, John T.; Rockwell, Vera C.; Albertson, Henry H.; Strain, John D.; Weston, Emma; Welling, Richard, Nov. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - King, Edward M.; Sargent, Noel; Osborne, Charles D.; McAllister, Peter F.; Wickware, F.G.; Bigelow, J.D.; Rockwell, Vera C. (Annotations.), Nov. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 33)
  - Rockwell, Vera C.; Wickware, F.G.; Freeborn, Malcolm J.; Cummings, Kate, Nov. 1937 (Box 37, Folder 34)
  - Eaker, Arthur T.; Wickware, F.G.; Hurley, John W.; Broadhurst, Iva; Rockwell, Vera C., Dec. 1937 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Rockwell, Vera C.; Wickware, F.G., Feb. - Dec.1937 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    Book reviews.
  - Rockwell, Vera C.; Wickware, F.G.; George, Edgar F., Jan. - Mar.1938 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Jacob G.; Wickware, F.G., Apr. - Jun.1938 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Albertson, Henry H.; Wickware, F.G.; King, Edward M.; Rockwell, Vera C., Jul. 1938 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Wickware, F.G.; Albertson, Henry H.; LeRoy, Betty; McFarland, J. Horace, Aug. - Nov.1938 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Welling, Richard, Dec. 1938 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    George Junior Republic Alumni Association.
  - Rockwell, Vera C., 1938 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Stoddart, Bessie D.; Perottino, Terziana; Welling, Richard, Jan. 1939 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Welling, Richard; Smith, Jacob G.; Roosevelt, Eleanor B. (Mrs. Theodore). Letter to Emma L. George concerning George Family genealogy; Untitled essay by Jacob G. Smith on self-government, Feb. 1939 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - George, Emma L.; George, Orra Kelsey; Dawson, Charles B.; Freeborn, Edith G.; Stoddart, Bessie D., Mar. - Apr.1939 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Kirkland, Eleanor G., May 1939 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Wickware, F.G.; Freeborn, Edith G.; Bartol, Leah, Jun. 1939 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Albertson, Henry H.; Hurley, John W.; London, Jack; Freeborn, Edith G., Jul. 1939 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    George Junior Republic press release; Daughters of the American Revolution; Text of memorial service.
  - Bartol, Leah, Aug. 1939 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Dawson, Charles B., Sept. 1939 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Forbes, Alexander; Dawson, Charles B.; Rockwell, Vera C.; Kirkland, J.B., Oct. - Nov.1939 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    "Foreword to the New Pioneers" by Jacob G. Smith.
  - Kirkland, J.B.; Broadhurst, Iva; Dawson, Charles B.; Freeborn, Edith G., Dec. 1939 (Box 38, Folder 18)
    Mrs. Daddy's park.
  - Welling, Richard, 1939 (Box 38, Folder 19)
    Junior Republic Yell.
  - McAllister, Peter F.; Smith, Jacob G.; Hotchkiss, Willard E., Jan. 1940 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - McAllister, Peter F.; Freeborn, Edith G., Feb. 1940 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Albertson, Henry H.; Kirkland, Eleanor G.; Parker, John A., Mar. 1940 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Rosenthal, Max, Apr. 1940 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Kirkland, Eleanor G.; Welling, Richard; Stowe, Lyman Beecher, May 1940 (Box 38, Folder 24)
    "Daddy George's New Project."
  - Kirkland, Eleanor G., Jun. 1940 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Smith, Jacob G., Jul. 1940 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Kirkland, Eleanor G., Aug. - Oct.1940 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - King, Edward M., Nov. 1940 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Barnes, Morgan; McAllister, Peter F.; Welling, Richard, Dec. 1940 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - King, Edward M., 1940 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Welling, Richard; Rockwell, Vera C., Jan. 1941 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Sargent, Noel; Christiancy, George A.C.; Tatnall, Samuel W.; Jaeger, Herman W., Feb. 1941 (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Forbes, Alexander, Mar. 1941 (Box 38, Folder 33)
    Testimonial to William R. George by Alexander Forbes.
  - Kirkland, Eleanor G., Apr. - May1941 (Box 38, Folder 34)
  - Kruse, Paul J.; King, Edward M., Jun. 1941 (Box 38, Folder 35)
  - Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Rockwell, Vera C.; Kruse, Paul J., Jul. 1941 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Testimonial to William R. George by Liberty Hyde Bailey.
  - Knight, Arthur C., Aug. - Sep.1941 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Knight, Arthur C.; Jaeger, Herman W.; Broadhurst, Iva, Oct. - Nov.1941 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - King, Edward M.; Stawinski, Johann, Dec. 1941 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Sweetland, Elizabeth J., 1941 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - A short history of the George Junior Republic by Edith G. Freeborn, 1941 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Frame, Nat T., Jan. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - War correspondence between Mrs. William R. George and ex-citizens serving in the military, Jan. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Searles, Frank H.; Broadhurst, Iva, Feb. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    War correspondence.
  - King, Edward M.; Jaeger, Herman W., Mar. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    "For Daddy George" by Vera C. Rockwell; War correspondence.
  - "Special Report to the Finance Committee of the Board of Directors - George Junior Republic" by Donald T. Urquhart, including photographs of Republic buildings, Mar. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - War correspondence, Apr. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - "Suggestions for Radio Interview"; War correspondence, Apr. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Broadhurst, Iva; Stawinski, Johann, May 1942 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    Report of the Finance Committee, George Junior Republic.
  - Broadhurst, Iva; Stawinski, Johann, May 1942 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Stawinski, Johann, May 1942 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - King, Edward M., Jun. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - "Comments on George Junior Republic" by Bessie Beatty; War correspondence, Jun. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Jaeger, Herman W., Jul. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - King, Edward M., Jul. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Stawinski, Johann; Kinane, John J., Aug. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - War correspondence, Sept. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Freeborn, Edith G., Sept. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - War correspondence, Oct. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Kinane, John J.; Jaeger, Herman W.; King, Edward M., Oct. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Stawinksi, Johann, Nov. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - King, Edward M., Nov. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - War correspondence, Dec. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - King, Edward M.; Dawson, Charles B., Dec. 1942 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - Kashmer, Anne, 1942 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Freeborn, Edith G.; Dapping, William O., 1942 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Jan. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - War correspondence; List of ex-citizens in the Service, Jan. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - War correspondence, Feb. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - War correspondence, Feb. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - War correspondence, Mar. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Broadhurst, Iva, Mar. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Bird, Macey, Apr. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - War correspondence, Apr. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Stawinski, Johann, May 1943 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Stawinski, Johann, May 1943 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Stawinski, Johann, May 1943 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - King, Edward M.; Stawinski, Johann, Jun. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Kinane, John J., Jun. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - War correspondence, Jun. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - King, Edward M.; Herbert, Wolcott Johnston, Jun. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Jul. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Eaker, Arthur T.; Stawinski, Johann, Jul. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Eaker, Arthur T.; Stowe, Lyman Beecher; Smith, Jacob G.; Stawinski, Johann, Jul. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Pyle, Enos A.; Smith, Jacob G., Jul. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    Constitution of the George Junior Republic; War correspondence.
  - Stawinski, Johann; Pyle, Enos A.; Smith, Jacob G., Aug. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Aug. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - King, Edward M., Aug. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Hurley, John W.; Stawinski, Johann, Aug. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Stawinski, Johann; Marchant, Margaret Fenner Jennison, Sept. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - War correspondence, Sept. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Stawinski, Johann; Christiancy, George A.C., Oct. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - War correspondence, Oct. 1943 (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Nov. 1943 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - War correspondence, Nov. 1943 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Dec. 1943 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Hurley, John W., Dec. 1943 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Pyle, Enos A., 1943 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Smith, Jacob G.; Pyle, Enos A., Jan. - Jul.1943 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - War correspondence, Aug. - Dec.1943 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - War correspondence, Jan. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - War correspondence, Jan. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Snyder, Esther, Jan. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - War correspondence, Feb. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - King, Edward M.; Stawinski, Johann; Freeborn, Edith G., Feb. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    War correspondence. (Annotations.)
  - War correspondence, Feb. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - War correspondence, Mar. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - War correspondence, Mar. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - War correspondence, Mar. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Apr. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - War correspondence, Apr. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - War correspondence, May 1944 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - War correspondence, May 1944 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Stawinski, Johann, May 1944 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    List of ex-citizens in the Service; War correspondence.
  - War correspondence, Jun. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Constitution of the George Junior Republic; War correspondence, Jun. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - King, Edward M., Jun. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - War correspondence, Jul. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - War correspondence, Jul. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Kinane, John J.; Lehman, Herbert H., Jul. 1944 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Moses, Horace A., Aug. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Albertson, Henry H., Aug. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Sargent, Noel, Aug. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Van Every, Luella; Stowe, Lyman Beecher, Aug. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Eaker, Arthur T., Sept. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Stawinski, Johann; Eaker, Arthur T.; Rosenthal, Max; Groopman, Henri, Sept. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - War correspondence, Sept. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Sept. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - War correspondence, Oct. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - War correspondence, Oct. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - War correspondence, Oct. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - War correspondence, Oct. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Eaker, Arthur T., Nov. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - War correspondence, Nov. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - War correspondence, Nov. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - War correspondence, Dec. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Day, Edmund Ezra, Dec. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - War correspondence, Dec. 1944 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Constitution of the George Junior Republic, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Stawinski, Johann, 1944 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    Delta Tau Delta Alumni Corporation Treasury.
  - War correspondence, Jan. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - War correspondence, Jan. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - War correspondence, Jan. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - War correspondence, Jan. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - War correspondence, Feb. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - War correspondence, Feb. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Feb. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 27)
  - War correspondence, Mar. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 28)
  - War correspondence, Mar. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 29)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Mar. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 30)
  - War correspondence, Mar. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 31)
  - War correspondence, Apr. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 32)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Apr. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 33)
  - War correspondence, Apr. 1945 (Box 42, Folder 34)
  - Jaeger, Herman W.; Stawinski, Johann, May 1945 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Forbes, Amelia, May 1945 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Stawinski, Johann, May 1945 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - War correspondence, May 1945 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Freeborn, Edith G., Jun. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Jun. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - War correspondence, Jun. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Eaker, Arthur T.; Albertson, Henry H., Jul. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - War correspondence, Jul. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - War correspondence, Jul. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - War correspondence, Aug. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - War correspondence, Aug. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Freeborn, Edith G., Aug. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Kirkland, Eleanor G., Sept. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Freeborn, Edith G., Sept. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - War correspondence, Oct. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - War correspondence, Oct. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - War correspondence, Nov. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - War correspondence, Nov. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Stawinski, Johann; Dawson, Charles B., Dec. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Stawinski, Johann; Kirkland, Eleanor G., Dec. 1945 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Groopman, Henri, 1942-45 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - War correspondence; Lists of ex-citizens in the Service, 1942-45 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Forbes, Stephen H.; Stawinski, Johann; Palmieri, Henry J., Jan. 1946 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Jan. 1946 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Feb. 1946 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Stawinski, Johann, Mar. 1946 (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - King, Edward M.; Stawinski, Johann, Apr. - May1946 (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - King, Edward M.; Urquhart, Donald T.; Eaker, Arthur T., Jun. 1946 (Box 43, Folder 29)
    Founders' Day.
  - Founders' Day, Jul. 1946 (Box 43, Folder 30)
  - Armstrong, Marguerite S.; Broadhurst, Iva; Naecker, Ruth, Jul. 1946 (Box 43, Folder 31)
  - Urquhart, Donald T.; Forbes, Stephen H.; Naecker, Ruth; London, Jack, Aug. 1946 (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Morris, David; Stoddart, Bessie D; McAllister, Catharine; Stawinski, Johann; Broadhurst, Iva; Rodier, Roscoe, Sept. 1946 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Armstrong, Marguerite S., Oct. 1946 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Candela, Michael; King, Edward M.; Stawinski, Johann; Yunker, Johnny; Fellows, Robert, Nov. 1946 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    George Junior Republic government.
  - Bartol, Leah; Fellows, Georgia, Dec. 1946 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    List of citizens present at 50th anniversary of the George Junior Republic. (Annotations.)
  - Beach, William G.; Freeborn, Edith G.; Levin, Leonard S.; Stralem, Donald S., Jan. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Armstrong, Marguerite S.; Hurley, Merton, Jan. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    "Some Post-war Impressions of the Educational Program of the George Junior Republic."
  - Levin, Leonard S., Feb. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Jacob G.; Miller, Gerrit Smith; Armstrong, Marguerite S.; Snyder, George W., Mar. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Kinane, John J., Apr. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    George Junior Republic Board of Directors.
  - Kinane, John J.; Korbas, Raymond J., May 1947 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - "Daddy George's Memorial Service" by Edith G. Freeborn, Jun. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Jacob G.; Vowe, Erich; Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Kinane, John J., Jun. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    "Do You Remember..." by John J. Kinane. (Annotations.)
  - Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Eaker, Arthur T.; Mahan, Ralph S.; Meriam, J.L., Jul. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Mahan, Ralph S., Jul. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    Speeches delivered at George Junior Republic.
  - Morgan, Evelyn Irene; Mangold, Barbara, Aug. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Armstrong, Marguerite S.; Bartol, Russell, Aug. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 16)
    George Junior Republic bar examination.
  - Ryan, D.M.; Cluett, Jean M.; Morgan, Evelyn Irene; Mahan, Ralph S. (Annotations.), Sept. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Albertson, Henry H.; Morgan, Evelyn Irene, Oct. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Jacob G.; Morgan, Evelyn Irene; Hurley, John M., Nov. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 19)
    List of George Junior Republic voting citizens; George Junior Republic inauguration; Address by Donald S. Stralem.
  - Forbes, Stephen H.; Bancroft, Thayer D.; Bartol, Leah, Dec. 1947 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Mahan, Ralph S., Jan. - Feb.1948 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Kruse, Paul J.; Forbes, Alexander; Welling, Richard, Mar. 1948 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Forbes, Alexander; Welling, Richard; Stoddart, Bessie D.; Brewster, C. Wesley; Smith, Alice; Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Urquhart, Donald T., Apr. - Jun.1948 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Albertson, Henry H.; Vowe, Erich; Ganyard, Mervin B.; Kinane, John J., Jul. 1948 (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Mayne, Herbert F.; Freeborn, Edith G.; Ganyard, Leslie; Gilbert, Richard H.; Forbes, Stephen H., Aug. - Sep1948 (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Gauffin, Einar; Vowe, Erich; Kinane, John J.; Eaker, Arthur T.; Levin, Leonard S. (Annotations.), Oct. - Dec.1948 (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - List of ex-citizens, 1948 (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Kinane, John J.; King, Edward M.; Spengeman, Edward C. (Annotations.), Jan. - Feb.1949 (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Brewster, C. Wesley; Spengeman, Edward C.; Norton, David M., Mar. 1949 (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Livingston, Bessie; Vowe, Erich, Apr. 1949 (Box 44, Folder 30)
    Article by Anna Larsen about visiting German sociologists. (Annotations.)
  - Morgan, Evelyn Irene; Stoddart, Bessie D., May - Jun.1949 (Box 44, Folder 31)
    Memorial address by John J. Kinane.
  - Hurley, John W.; Stawinski, Johann; Smith, Jacob G., Jul. 1949 (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Hurley, John W.; Vowe, Erich; Albertson, Henry H.; Freeborn, Edith G., Aug. 1949 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    List of ex-citizens present for Founder's Day.
  - Hurley, Jack; Allen, Sanford H., Sept. 1949 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Hurley, Jack, Oct. 1949 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Vowe, Erich; Hurley, John W.; Hurley, Jack; Perry, Edward W. (Annotations.), Nov. 1949 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Hurley, Jack; Hurley, John W.; Freeborn, Edith G. (Annotations.), Dec. 1949 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Hurley, John W.; Smith, Jacob G., Jan. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    George Junior Republic coins.
  - Hurley, Jack; Hurley, John W.; Forbes, Alexander; King, Edward M.; Kinane, John J. (Annotations.), Jan. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Urquhart, Donald T.; Hurley, Jack; Smith, Jacob G.; Hurley, John W., Feb. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Hurley, Jack; Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Perry, Edward W.; Atkinson, Harry W., Feb. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Atkinson, Harry W.; Hurley, Jack; Hurley, John W.; Smith, Jacob G.; Albertson, Henry H. (Annotations.), Mar. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Vowe, Erich; Hurley, Jack; Hurley, John W., Apr. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Hurley, Jack; Hurley, John W.; Perry, Edward W., May 1950 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Hurley, John W.; Albertson, Henry H.; Hurley, Jack, Jun. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    "The Meaning of Education in a Junior Republic."
  - Hurley, John W., Jul. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    "Daddy George - The Man and His Ideal."
  - Biggs, Helene Boucher; Fenner, Phyllis; Hurley, John W.; Perry, Edward W., Jul. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Hurley, Jack; Genung, Albert B.; Ganyard, Mervin B.; Smith, Jacob G., Aug. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Ganyard, Mervin B.; Hurley, John W., Sept. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Larsen, Anna, Oct. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Albertson, Henry H.; Hurley, John W.; Dentler, Frances Rockwell, Nov. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 18)
    Jacob G. Smith Memorial; George Junior Republic inauguration.
  - Palmieri, Henry J.; Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Hurley, John W.; Hoover, Herbert, Dec. 1950 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Forbes, Alexander; Freeborn, Edith G.; Kinane, John J., Jan. 1951 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Ganyard, Leslie; Kinane, John J.; Hotchkiss, Willard E.; Marshall, Robert C., Feb. 1951 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Carrol-Abbing, John Patrick; Freer, Frank; Vowe, Erich; Rogers, Mary Pickford, Mar. 1951 (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - McDonald, Angus L., Apr. 1951 (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Forbes, Alexander; McBain, Frances, May - Jun.1951 (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Urquhart, Donald T.; Stawinski, Johann, Jul. 1951 (Box 45, Folder 25)
    Memorial Service.
  - Norton, David M.; Garimaldi, Edward, Aug. 1951 (Box 45, Folder 26)
  - Norton, David M.; Steinmetz, Elsie Johnson; Carrol-Abbing, John Patrick; Sweetland, Libbie J., Sept. 1951 (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Kelly, Bradley; Norton, David M.; Berry, Romeyn, Oct. - Nov.1951 (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Kinane, John J.; Vowe, Erich, Dec. 1951 (Box 45, Folder 29)
  - Palmieri, Henry J.; Vowe, Erich, Jan. - Feb.1952 (Box 45, Folder 30)
  - Hurley, John W.; Mahan, Ralph S.; Vowe, Erich; Rogers, Mary Pickford; Albertson, Henry H., Mar. - Apr.1952 (Box 45, Folder 31)